Keter Perry - Full Stack Developer

Tel: 050-7744085, Email: keterav@gmail.com, GitHub, LinkedIn

After a long career as an experienced and dedicated English lecturer in which I have demonstrated outstanding proficiency in colleges, high schools, and elementary schools for over ten years in both formal and informal education, I have resolved on making a career change, studying programming. I hold a Master's Degree and a Bachelor's Degree (Hons) in English Linguistics, and I am now seeking a Full Stack Developer position.

EDUCATION

2022

Full Stack Developer -Bootcamp-Appleseeds, Intensive 6-months, 720 hours training program that encourages self-led learning and group projects that simulate real-world development teams. Applying front and back skills.

- Mid Project: The project depicts a textbook store that was built as part of my dream to help kids improve their English-speaking skills and currently constitutes the basis for upcoming English workbooks. Technologies used: HTML, CSS, React, Demo Cod
- Final Project: This project is all about food, a site for all food fans (like me) in which they can talk and share their knowledge of food. Technologies used: HTML, CSS, React, Node.js, Express, MongoDB, Socket.io, MUI, Final Project

2017-2020 N	Aastar's Dagraa	in Fnalich linguistics	. Ben Gurion University of the Negey	,

2010-2011 Teaching Certificate in English, Ben Gurion University of the Negev.

2007-2010 Bachelor's Degree in English Linguistics and Education, Ben Gurion University of the Negev.

*Graduation with honors

EMPLOYMENT

2022-today	Working on di	fferent personal	nrojects +	self-learning
ZUZZ-LUGGV	VVOINING ON ON	11616116 DC1301141	, DIOICCL3 , .	ocii icarriire

2019-2021 English lecturer for advanced courses, Hemdat HaDarom college

Cooperating with various internal work interfaces, Working closely with other crews.

2019-2021 5 points English teacher, Gutwirth school

Specializing in Matriculation examinations (Bagrut exam) in high school.

Planning and leading projects in junior high.

2017- 2020 Tutoring business owner

Managing a thriving private business teaching English and Mathematics to students of all levels.

Organizing a large-scale work, a timeline and milestones of what needs to be done.

Keeping track of students' achievements and progress and in charge of cash flow, income and expenses.

2011-2016 Elementary English teacher

TECHNICAL KNOWLEDGE

HTML, CSS, JS, React, TS, Node.js, MongoDB, SQL, C, C++ (self-learning), Data Structures (She Codes), GIT, Postman

NATIONAL SERVICE

2005-2007 Rabin Medical Center, Petah Tikva, Israel

Performed various administrative tasks involving teamwork, multi-tasking, and initiative thinking, including managing files and responsibility for general office duties.

LANGUAGES

Hebrew- Native English - Native level